PAUL: Oh, oh.
PAUL：哦，哦。
JAKE: Whoa, Jesus, man.
杰克：哇，耶稣，伙计。
PAUL: Sorry.
PAUL：对不起。
[LAUGHTER]
[笑声]
How do you fancy a game of football?
您如何看待足球比赛？
JAKE: Well, as long as it's not you playing,
杰克：好吧，只要不是你在玩，
mate, because that was ridiculous.
伴侣，因为那太荒谬了。
PAUL: All right.
PAUL：好的。
Wa!
！
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]
JAKE: What time does the game start?
杰克：游戏什么时候开始？
PAUL: Uh-- Tuesday.
PAUL：嗯-星期二。
JAKE: Hmm.
杰克：嗯。
That was a wasted journey then.
那时那是一次浪费的旅程。
PAUL: We got nice ponchos out of it though.
PAUL：不过，我们得到了很好的雨披。
JAKE: Mhm.
杰克：嗯。
PAUL: That'll work fine for England.
PAUL：对英格兰来说会很好。
JAKE: It's going to be tough, isn't it?
杰克：很难，不是吗？
PAUL: Why?
保罗：为什么？
JAKE: HTTP2.
杰克：HTTP2。
JAKE: Well, we have to turn around and say--
杰克：好吧，我们得转身说-
PAUL: LOL, no.
PAUL：大声笑，不。
JAKE: Sorry, guys.
杰克：对不起，伙计们。
PAUL: Yeah, it's all broken isn't it?
PAUL：是的，这全都坏了吧？
JAKE: You know that stuff we said?
杰克：你知道我们说的话吗？
We were lying.
我们在说谎。
We've got to change everything that you do.
我们必须改变您所做的一切。
With HTTP2, the rules all change.
使用HTTP2，规则全部更改。
PAUL: Yes.
保罗：是的。
Because well, let's think this through, right?
因为好，让我们仔细考虑一下，对吧？
Because the requests, they're not as expensive anymore,
由于这些请求，它们不再那么昂贵，
are they?
是吗
Because you've got, what is it?
因为有，这是什么？
One TCP stream or whatever?
一个TCP流还是其他？
JAKE: Yeah, yeah.
杰克：是的，是的。
With HTTP2, you've got one stream, one connection, even.
使用HTTP2，您甚至只有一个流，一个连接。
So requesting new files, it does not
因此，请求新文件不会
have to open a new connection.
必须打开一个新的连接。
It's just all part of the multiplex stream.
它只是复用流的所有部分。
PAUL: So now you what?
PAUL：那你现在呢？
Like, you can send down-- or you send all these separate files.
就像，您可以向下发送-或发送所有这些单独的文件。
So spriting goes away.
因此精神消失了。
Concatenation goes away.
串联消失。
You still in line?
你还在排队吗？
No, you probably wouldn't.
不，您可能不会。
Would you?
你会？
JAKE: Well, probably not, no.
杰克：好吧，可能不是。
I mean, you're still going to have the request and response.
我的意思是，您仍然需要请求和响应。
But all those headers are compressed.
但是所有这些标头都是压缩的。
PAUL: Oh yeah, yeah.
PAUL：哦，是的。
JAKE: Because they're a big deal.
杰克：因为他们很重要。
Like, in HTTP1, you've got, like, a K and a half of headers
就像在HTTP1中一样，您有一个K和一半的标题
sometimes with cookies and that.
有时还有饼干等等。
If you multiply that by, like, 18
如果乘以18
requested a page, that really stacks up.
请求一个页面，该页面真的会堆积起来。
PAUL: Yeah, yep.
PAUL：是的。
Yep.
是的
JAKE: And compression just takes care of that.
杰克：压缩就好了。
Because you don't have the slow start for most of it as well.
因为大多数情况下您也没有很慢的开始。
Because you're on that single TCP connection.
因为您在那个TCP连接上。
Yes.
是。
And so I guess you're probably the same as me.
所以我想你可能和我一样。
When you write CSS, do you have, like,
编写CSS时，您是否有喜欢
a CSS file for components and stuff?
组件和物品的CSS文件？
PAUL: Yeah, pretty much.
PAUL：是的，差不多。
I'd say so, thereabouts.
我会这么说，大约。
JAKE: I think we can get to a point
杰克：我想我们可以说到重点
where we just serve all of those files separately.
我们只是单独提供所有这些文件。
PAUL: That sounds really, really nice, actually.
PAUL：听起来确实非常非常好。
Because it reduces that build step quite a bit, really.
因为它确实大大减少了构建步骤。
You know?
你懂？
You just, sort of-- here's the thing I made.
您只是，这是我做的。
Push it up live.
现场直播。
That's good.
那很好。
Actually, talking pushing, that's
其实说推就是
another thing about HTTP2 as well, isn't it?
还有关于HTTP2的另一件事，不是吗？
And you know, you can request one file and get all those.
而且您知道，您可以请求一个文件并获取所有文件。
JAKE: Yeah.
杰克：是的。
You could say, oh, you want the page?
您可以说，哦，您想要页面吗？
Well, I'm going to give you the page.
好吧，我要给你页面。
But-- special bonus prize-- here's some CSS.
但是-特别奖金-这是一些CSS。
Here's some JavaScript that I know you're going to need.
这是我知道您需要的一些JavaScript。
And it will say, like, here's what
它会说，这就是
your request would look like.
您的请求看起来像。
And here comes the response.
回应来了。
Just going to throw it at you.
只是把它扔给你。
PAUL: Downer-- what if you've already got it?
PAUL：唐纳-如果您已经掌握了该怎么办？
JAKE: So yeah, I was looking at this.
杰克：是的，我在看这个。
The client actually can send an RST_Stream packet.
客户端实际上可以发送RST_Stream数据包。
PAUL: Oh, wow, that's catchy.
PAUL：哦，哇，很吸引人。
JAKE: Yeah.
杰克：是的。
And that's going to tell it to identify a particular stream
这将告诉它识别特定的流
and say, could you not, mate?
说，你不能，伴侣吗？
PAUL: Could you just back off?
PAUL：您可以退后吗？
Yeah?
是啊
JAKE: Could you stop that?
杰克：你能阻止吗？
PAUL: I've already this--
PAUL：我已经知道了
JAKE: Already got it.
杰克：已经知道了。
PAUL: Yeah.
PAUL：是的。
JAKE: And you can end up with a situation where you know,
杰克：你最终可能会遇到一个情况，
by the time you send that to the other side,
当您将其发送到另一端时，
it's already sent you an entire file anyway.
无论如何，它已经向您发送了整个文件。
So there's going to be some wasted bites.
因此，将有一些浪费的食物。
PAUL: And we don't know that's too bad though, right?
PAUL：而且我们不知道那太糟了吧？
JAKE: We don't think it's too bad.
杰克：我们认为这还不错。
Yeah.
是的
PAUL: It's probably better that way around
PAUL：这样可能更好
than having to request everything over and over
而不是一遍又一遍地要求一切
and over again.
一遍又一遍。
So OK, you decide you're going to ignore Paul and Jake's
好吧，您决定要忽略保罗和杰克的
advice-- wisely-- because say, HTTP2's kicking off.
建议-明智地-因为HTTP2的启动。
But the thing is, not every client
但问题是，并非每个客户
is going to be HTTP2 aware.
将意识到HTTP2。
Right?
对？
You still got HTTP1 clients.
您仍然拥有HTTP1客户端。
So how is a developer gonna kind of handle both?
那么开发人员如何同时处理这两种情况呢？
JAKE: Well, I mean, the servers are going to take care of that
杰克：好吧，我的意思是，服务器将负责处理该问题。
automatically.
自动。
But I take your question.
但我接受你的问题。
I take your point.
我明白你的意思。
We've got this issue of do you, as a developer,
作为开发人员，您有这个问题吗？
play to HTTP2 strengths?
发挥HTTP2的优势？
Or do you kind of fudge it for HTTP1?
还是您对HTTP1有所怀疑？
PAUL: I reckon if you built something
PAUL：我认为你是否建造了东西
that only works in evergreen browsers,
仅适用于常绿浏览器，
you're probably safe to be like, oh, I'm
你可能会很安全，就像，哦，我是
just going to do HTTP2, right?
只是要做HTTP2，对吧？
JAKE: Yeah, so multiple CSS files, multiple JS files,
杰克：是的，所以有多个CSS文件，多个JS文件，
everything's sweet.
一切都很好。
PAUL: Well, I reckon, oh, the HTTP2,
PAUL：嗯，我想，哦，HTTP2，
it sends an upgrade header, doesn't it?
它发送一个升级头，不是吗？
JAKE: Yes, it does.
杰克：是的，确实如此。
PAUL: So you could differentiate on that.
PAUL：所以您可以在这方面有所区别。
You could be, like, uh, if I get that upgrade header,
如果我得到了升级标头，您可能会像，
I'm going to send you the HTTP2 version.
我将向您发送HTTP2版本。
JAKE: Oh, I see what you're talking about.
杰克：哦，我明白你在说什么。
PAUL: So then you might build two versions in your
PAUL：那么您可能会在自己的版本中建立两个版本
build scripts.
构建脚本。
So like, concatenate in one, not concatenate in the other,
就像，在一个中串联，而不在另一个中串联，
and then, basically, differentiate
然后，基本上，区分
based on that header, whether you're going to-- which one
根据该标题，您是否要去哪一个？
you're going to serve up.
你会发球。
JAKE: So you cater for both?
杰克：你们两者兼得？
PAUL: Ah ha ha!
PAUL：啊哈哈！
Winner, winner, chicken dinner.
冠军，冠军，鸡肉晚餐。
JAKE: Oh, that's a good idea.
杰克：哦，那是个好主意。
PAUL: I like it.
PAUL：我喜欢。
JAKE: One of the things I'm real hoping for is the edge caching
杰克：我真正希望的一件事是边缘缓存
services, like CloudFlare, Akamai, the CDNs, I mean,
服务，例如CloudFlare，Akamai，CDN，
they're already supporting things like SPDY.
他们已经在支持SPDY。
I think Akamai supports HTTP2 already.
我认为Akamai已经支持HTTP2。
What I really want to see from those guys
我真的很想从那些家伙那里看到
is for them to understand particular headers
让他们了解特定的标题
that our service would send.
我们的服务会发送。
So even if you're running HTTP 1.1,
因此，即使您正在运行HTTP 1.1，
you could send along, like, a link prefetch header.
您可以像发送链接预取标头一样发送。
And it would interpret that as an HTTP2 push.
它会将其解释为HTTP2推送。
PAUL: So that's kind of like a halfway house.
PAUL：这有点像中途之家。
It's like, my server's not ready to go HTTP2 entirely.
就像我的服务器还没准备好完全使用HTTP2一样。
But if I give you these additional bits
但是如果我给你这些额外的东西
of a nudge, then the people who do understand it,
轻推一下，然后那些真正了解它的人，
you're just giving them just that little bit of an edge
你只是给他们一点点优势
over what you're doing.
在做什么。
JAKE: Yeah.
杰克：是的。
PAUL: Yeah, I like that.
PAUL：是的，我喜欢。
JAKE: So you can even send, like, an x-header say, oh, you
杰克：所以你甚至可以发送一个x标题，说，哦，你
know, x priority or something.
知道，x优先级或其他。
That would be the signal to the HTTP2 part at the end that
那将是最后向HTTP2部分发出的信号
can sort of do the right thing with that stuff,
可以用这些东西做正确的事，
send the right frames in the data stream.
在数据流中发送正确的帧。
PAUL: In any case, I'm sold.
PAUL：无论如何，我被卖了。
I think it's going to be great.
我认为这将会很棒。
I suspect we probably just need to issue an apology to pretty
我怀疑我们可能只需要道歉就可以了。
much every developer that we've misadvised
我们误导了每个开发人员
over the last few years.
在过去几年间。
JAKE: Any performance talk before this time
杰克：在此之前的任何表演演讲
is null and void.
是无效的。
PAUL: That's-- yeah.
PAUL：是的。
JAKE: Going to make us look pretty silly, isn't it?
杰克：会让我们看起来很傻，不是吗？
PAUL: Well, that's going to be awkward.
PAUL：嗯，这很尴尬。
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]